danieldefense.com 2017-03-14

# PRIVACY POLICY/DISCLAIMERS | Daniel Defense

This Website Privacy Policy, Terms of Use, and Disclaimer (collectively referred to as “Privacy Policy”) is provided by Daniel Defense, Inc., and its affiliates, including M. C. Daniel Group, Inc., Daniel Defense Armament, Inc., Ambush Firearms, Inc., and Daniel Concepts, Inc. (collectively referred to as the “Daniel Companies,” “we,” “our,” or “us”).  The Privacy Policy is applicable to our websites [www.danieldefense.com](http://www.danieldefense.com/) and [www.ambushfirearms.com](http://www.ambushfirearms.com/) (collectively referred to as "Websites"), and it governs data collection and your usage of our Websites.  It does not apply to information we obtain or collect through means other than our Websites.

PLEASE READ THIS WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING AND/OR USING OUR WEBSITES, YOU ACCEPT AND AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND DISCLAIMERS OF THE PRIVACY POLICY AS IT MAY BE AMENDED OR MODIFIED FROM TIME TO TIME AS DESCRIBED HEREIN BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO SUCH TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND DISCLAIMERS, DO NOT ACCESS OUR WEBSITES.

Data Collection

This Privacy Policy includes a description of our policies with respect to our collection and use of certain information through our Website. We may collect two types of information from you: (a) personal information that you voluntarily provide to us, and (b) usage information concerning our Websites that we automatically collect as you interact with our Websites.

a) Personal Information that You Voluntarily Provide to Us

The majority of times that you visit our Websites, your use can occur without you telling us who you are and without providing any information about yourself. However, there are times that we may ask you to voluntarily provide information ("Personal Information") about yourself through the Websites.  Our requests for personal information will only occur to serve specific purposes, including, but not limited to, (1) your purchase of our products; (2) for you to receive our newsletters; (3) for you to participate in user surveys; (4) to process your registration with our Websites, including verifying that your e-mail address is active and valid; (5) to improve our Websites; (6) to communicate with you regarding information such as products, services, or offers, which we believe you may be interested; (7) to respond to your inquiries; (8) to contact you regarding any of our contests, sweepstakes, or promotions within which you have participated: (9) for our own internal business purposes; and (10) for other purposes as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. 

We will not sell, rent, or lease your Personal Information to third parties. However, we may need to provide limited Personal Information to third parties for the purposes of processing orders, processing credit card and other payment transactions, and to deliver products or services to you that you have purchased. Personal financial information will only be used for the reason it was provided, such as to complete a purchase. You are under no obligation to provide us with Personal Information. However, your refusal to provide requested Personal Information will likely limit your ability to participate in certain services or activities offered on our Websites, particularly when the requested Personal Information is noted as being mandatory or required for you to participate in a particular service or activity.

b) Information We May Automatically Collect

Our Websites may use “cookies” or other programs or tracking technologies to collect basic information from you as you use our Websites (“Automatically Collected Information”). A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used for various purposes to collect information about activity at our Websites. Some cookies may be used to recall Personal Information that you previously provided when you used our Websites. This Automatically Collected Information is generally used to enhance and personalize your web experience with us, and to provide us with basic information about how users access and benefit from our Websites. Such Automatically Collected Information may include, but is not limited to, your IP address, browser, duration of time on our Websites, what pages were viewed at our Websites, the duration of time on pages within our Websites, keywords searched at our Websites, products purchased through our Websites, the language you use at our Websites, your operating system, and what you clicked on at our Websites.  You have the option of blocking or deleting cookies through the use of your browser.  However, if you block or delete cookies your use and enjoyment of our Websites may be impaired.

Consent to Transfer Information to the United States

All of our Websites are operated in the United States and all information our Websites collect will be processed and stored in databases located in the United States. Thus, if you are in a location outside of the United States, by using our Websites you consent to the transfer to and processing of your information in the United States.

Our Policies Regarding Children

If you are under 18 years of age, please do not submit any information without the express consent and participation of a parent or guardian. We will not knowingly collect Personal Information about any person under 13 years of age. If you believe that we have information from or about anyone under 13 years of age, please notify us by email at: [webadmin@danieldefense.com](mailto:webadmin@danieldefense.com). 

Our Website Security

We will take commercially reasonable security measures to protect and secure your Personal Information. However, no transmission of data over the Internet or electronic storage of information can be 100% secure. Thus, while the Daniel Companies strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot warrant the security of any Personal Information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your Personal Information, we make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure its security in our systems.

Consent to Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time, which change will be effective 7 days following us posting a revised Privacy Policy on our Websites. Your continued use of our Websites 7 days following such posting means you accept and consent to those changes.

Contests, Sweepstakes, and Promotions

 We may, from time to time, at our sole discretion, offer contests, sweepstakes, and other promotions (collectively referred to as "Contests") through our Websites.  If you choose to participate in a Contest, Personal Information about you may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the Contest as required by applicable law or the rules that govern the Contest.  Such Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, announcement of winners and prize fulfillment.  Additionally, by participating in a Contest, you are agreeing and consenting to the official rules that govern such Contest.

Business Transfers and Corporate Changes

We reserve the right to disclose and transfer Personal Information to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of one or more of the Websites, or in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, or restructuring, corporate sale, or other corporate change, including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process.

Required Disclosures

We may disclose your personal information, without notice to you, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to the requirements of the law or comply with legal process served on the Daniel Companies; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of the Daniel Companies; or (3) under exigent circumstances, to protect the personal safety of users of our Websites or the public.

Ownership

One or more of the Daniel Companies owns all the information presented on our Websites and has copyrights on such information. All opinions, ideas, suggestions, and other feedback submitted through our Websites may be used by us, without any restriction and without charge, and nothing contained in this Privacy Policy shall limit or otherwise affect this.

Public Message Boards/Reviews

If you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through public message boards available through our Websites, such information may be collected and used by third parties and is not subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Additionally our Websites may provide opportunities for you to post reviews of our products and services. Such reviews are not subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Further, although we are not required to monitor such reviews, we reserve the right to remove any reviews that we, in our sole discretion, find offensive, abusive, racist, sexist, homophobic, sexually explicit, or otherwise objectionable. Additionally, we may remove such reviews if they contain information personal to you or others, such as email addresses, phone numbers, names, addresses, or website addresses.

 DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES

THE WEBSITES ARE PROVIDED "AS-IS", AND THE DANIEL COMPANIES DISCLAIM TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW ALL WARRANTIES RELATING TO THE WEBSITES, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THE WEBSITES, THE CONTENTS, INFORMATION, AND MATERIALS OF THE WEBSITES, WHETHER SUCH WARRANTIES  ARE EXPRESS, IMPLIED, OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR TITLE, WARRANTIES ARISING FROM COURSE OF DEALING OR USAGE OF TRADE, OR WARRANTIES AGAINST INFRINGEMENT OR INTERFERENCE WITH ENJOYMENT. BY WAY OF EXAMPLE, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE DANIEL COMPANES DO NOT WARRANT THAT THE WEBSITES WILL FULFILL ANY USER'S PARTICULAR REQUIREMENTS OR EXPECTATIONS, THAT ACCESS TO THE WEBSITES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE, OR THAT ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITES IS ACCURATE.  SPECIFIC WARANTIES OFFERED BY US ON ANY PRODUCTS SOLD ON OUR WEBSITES GOVERN OVER THE DISCLAIMERS CONTAINED IN THIS PARAGRAPH.

 DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY

NEITHER THE DANIEL COMPANIES NOR ANY OF THEIR AFFILIATES, LICENSORS, PARTNERS, MANAGERS, SHAREHOLDERS, DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, AGENTS, OR EMPLOYEES SHALL HAVE ANY RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY TO ANY USER FOR ANY DAMAGES, WHETHER GENERAL, SPECIAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL, INCLUDING ANY LOST PROFITS, WHETHER OR NOT FORESEEABLE AND WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, COMMON LAW, OR ANY OTHER THEORY OF LIABILITY, STATUTE, OR REGULATION. USER EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGES AND AGREES THAT THE DANIEL COMPANIES ARE PROVIDING ACCESS TO THE WEBSITES IN RELIANCE ON THE DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND FURTHER ACKNOWLEDGES AND AGREES THAT SUCH DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATIONS ARE REASONABLE. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE DANIEL COMPANIES' LIABILITY TO ANY USER EXCEED THE AMOUNTS ACTUALLY PAID BY USER FOR USE OF THE WEBSITES.

 Pricing/Specifications

Prices and specifications for any products or services sold through our Websites are subject to change without notice.  Typographic, photographic, and /or descriptive errors are subject to correction.  In the event that we determine, in our sole discretion, that we have made an error concerning, but not limited to, the price, specification, quantity, or description of one or more of our products or services, any sale or transfer of said products or services shall be made subject to our correction(s). All prices are quoted in US$.

We welcome your questions and comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that we have not followed our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [webadmin@danieldefense.com](mailto:webadmin@danieldefense.com).

This Privacy Policy was last updated March 14, 2012.
